<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Explore Bitcoin and the Lightning Network: From Theory to Practice</title>
    <link>https://pesvi.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Explore Bitcoin and the Lightning Network: From Theory to Practice</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>english</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pesvi.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Grouphug - Batching transactions without interaction between users</title>
      <link>https://pesvi.xyz/posts/grouphug/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pesvi.xyz/posts/grouphug/</guid>
      <description>How GroupHug works, a server programmed in Rust that allows grouping or batching of transactions without interaction between users using SigHash Single | AnyoneCanPay</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to make a transaction with UTXOs of different wallets with Sparrow</title>
      <link>https://pesvi.xyz/posts/psbt_sparrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pesvi.xyz/posts/psbt_sparrow/</guid>
      <description>How to make a Coinjoin or a grouping of transactions without interaction between users using Sparrow Wallet and Bitcoin Core</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pesvi.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pesvi.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>About me I am a PhD student doing research at the Department of Information and Communication Engineering (DEiC) at the Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona (UAB).
My current interests are Bitcoin, the Lightning Network and protocols on top of Bitcoin. In fact, these are the topics on which I do research 😉. Apart from Bitcoin related topics, I am also passionate about cryptography, privacy, cybersecurity and programming.
Pd. You can report errors in the posts to Github, I will correct them as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pesvi.xyz/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pesvi.xyz/publications/</guid>
      <description>Google Schoolar Profile
Papers Pol Espinasa-Vilarrasa, Sílvia Sanvicente, Cristina Pérez-Solà, and Jordi Herrera-Joancomartí. &amp;ldquo;Decision Tree Based Inference of Lightning Network Client Implementations.&amp;rdquo; In International Conference on Modeling Decisions for Artificial Intelligence, pp. 103-114. Cham: Springer Nature Switzerland, 2024.
[ GoogleSchoolar | Cite BibTeX ]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pesvi.xyz/pullrequests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pesvi.xyz/pullrequests/</guid>
      <description>Find here a list of my PRs and contributions to different Bitcoin related open source projects.
Bitcoin Core My Bitcoin Core Workspace
#31278 - wallet, rpc: Settxfeerate
Status → Obert
#31252 - rpc: print P2WSH witScript in getrawtransaction
Status → Obert
#31177 - rpc, logging: return &amp;ldquo;verificationprogress&amp;rdquo; of 1 when up to date
Status → Obert</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
